Resume.md 8/26/2018

Professional Experience

Profile:

Joshua Mason is a Technical Consultant for IBM's Client Innovation Center. Most of Josh's background in computer science has been self-motivated by his compassion for programming. He has worked mostly on game development for a few years while attending college. Josh is a graduate of Frostburg State University with a Bachelor's in Mathematics.

Career History:

7/2018 - CURRENT

IBM Global Business Services, US. Technical Consultant:

- Recently hired for IBM's Client Innovation Center.
- Completed Global Blue Consulting and DevOps training.
- Currently working on Innovation Garage project.

8/2017 - 5/2018

Allegany College of Maryland, US. Learning Specialist, Tutoring:

- Offered walk-in tutoring for both math and computer science courses.
- System Management: Controlled the tutoring management system for logging sessions between tutors and students.
- Teamwork: Collaborated with other tutors to enhance the learning expience of the students.

IBM Assignment History:

7/2018 - CURRENT

IBM Global Business Services, US Innovation Garage Project Description: Working in an Agile team to learn about DevOps and Automation Testing. Contribution:

Key Skills:

Languages:

- Proficient Knowledge: Java and Mathematica.
- Basic Knowledge: Lua, JavaScript, HTML, and MATLAB.

Familiar with:

NetBeans and Eclipse

Resume.md 8/26/2018

Key Courses and Training:

• Computer Science: Advanced Object Oriented Programming and Data Structures (Java), Intro to Computer Science I and II (Java).

- Mathematics: Number Theory, Geometry, Calculus, Set Theory, Differential Equations, Mathematical Models and Applications, and Linear Algebra.
- IBM Training: Agile, DevOps, Automation Testing.

Education

Qualifications:

- Bachelor's, Mathematics Frostburg State University, US, 2018
- Associate's, Mathematics Allegany College of Maryland, US, 2016